Let's name some black radicals.
Malcolm X, the Black Panthers, which of course includes Chairman Fred Hampton, George Jackson, Kathleen Cleaver, Huey P. Newton.
This is the black radical tradition.
June Jordan, Angela Davis, Paul Robeson, Dick Gregory, Toni Morrison.
Manning Marable, Robin D.G. Kelly, Joy James, Nikki Giovanni.
This is the black radical tradition.
James Baldwin, Nina Simone, Gil Scott Heron, Muhammad Ali.
Public Enemy, Sister Soulja, Amira Baraka, Alice Walker.
This is the black radical tradition.
Miriam Kaba.
Dr. Mark Lamont Hill.
Myself.
This is the black radical tradition.
The tradition of thinking radically that everybody deserves the right to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness without any injunction made by corporatists, made by capitalism, made by racism, etc.
We continue to also center education because we understand education as not simply just a means to an end, but a means for change.
What I will kill you to the right light whoops with drawn confidence is not just a meaning.
Then will come in to draw a vision of a Frankenstein-like feeling.
What is your status to the right to begin with father-centered mercie?
This will be taking place with action OLLEN KHANES.
Let's go back in the entry to Empire Field, Man.
This will be the disease to현.
bri.
This will come and share your life with the standard tradition that shall not help you
and invest as not only as the
truth is saluting to their heart.